A Guide to the Thomas N. Downing Papers, 1947-1977
Library of Virginia
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 485)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Banking, Currency and Housing--New York City Default (2 folders)
    - Budget Committee
    - District of Columbia Committee
    - Education and Labor (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 486)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Education and Labor (4 folders)
    - Education and Labor--Appropriations
    - Education and Labor--Child and Family Services Act (H.R. 2966) (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 487)
  - Committees and [General Legislation].
    - Education and Labor--Child and Family Services Act (1 folder)
    - Education and Labor--Minimum Wage--Agriculture and Retail
    - Education and Labor--Situs Picketing (H.R. 5900)
    - Education and Labor--Unemployment Compensation (H.R. 10210)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee (2 folders)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee--Appropriations
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 488)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Government Operations
    - Government Operations--Agency for Consumer Protection (H.R. 7575)
    - Government Operations--Consumer Cost Evaluation Act
    - Government Operations--Women's Conference (H.R. 9924)
    - Government Operations--General Revenue Sharing
    - House Administration
    - House Administration--Postcard Registration
    - Select Committee on Intelligence
    - Interior and Insular Affairs (1 folder).
      Note: This folder of Interior and Insular Affairs records contains a printed genealogy of the Overstreet Family, Saints and Black Sheep, by Kenneth Crouch.
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 489)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Interior and Insular Affairs (1 folder)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs--New River
    - Interior and Insular Affairs--Assateague Island Wilderness
    - Interior and Insular Affairs--Potomac Heritage Trail
    - Interior and Insular Affairs--Strip Mining
    - Internal Security Committee
    - International Relations
    - International Relations--Aid to Israel
    - International Relations--Jordan--Sale of Missiles
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 490)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - International Relations--Aid to Turkey (H.R. 2230)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (4 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 491)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (2 folders)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Clean Air Act Amendments
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--ConRail
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Consumer Cost Evaluation Act
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Energy Conservation and Oil Policy Act (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 492)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Energy Conservation and Oil Policy Act (2 folders)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Food Supplement
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Natural Gas
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--No-Fault Insurance
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Public Health Service Hospital
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Railroad Revitalization and Regulatory Reform Act of 1975
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Right to Food
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Truckers--Highway Amendment
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Vitamin Regulation
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 493)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee (4 folders)
    - Judiciary Committee--Abortion.
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 494)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee--Abortion Legislation
    - Judiciary Committee--Capital Punishment
    - Judiciary Committee--Copyright Bill (S. 22; H.R. 2223)
    - Judiciary Committee--Criminal Justice Reform Act of 1975 (2 folders)
    - Judiciary Committee--Gun Control
    - Judiciary Committee--Prayer
    - General Legislation (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 495)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - General Legislation (4 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 496)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - General Legislation--Old
    - General Legislation--Energy/Economy--President's Program (4 folders)
    - General Legislation--Letters from School Kids--12th Grade
    - General Legislation--NFIB Mandate Ballots 389-391 (3 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 497)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - General Legislation--NFIB Mandate Ballots 392-394, 396 (4 folders)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - Select Committee on Missing Persons in Southeast Asia
    - Ad Hoc Select Committee on Outer Continental Shelf
    - Post Office and Civil Service (4 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 498)
  - Committees and [General Legislation].
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Unionization (H.R. 55)
    - Post Office and Civil Service--1% Add-On--Cost of Living
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Hatch Act Reform (2 folders)
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Subcommittee on Postal Service
    - Post Office and Civil Service--8.66% Salary Increase (H.R. 688)
    - Public Works and Transportation (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 499)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Public Works and Transportation--Appalachian Regional Commission
    - Public Works and Transportation--Water Pollution--Sewage
    - Rules Committee
    - Science and Astronautics Committee
    - Science and Technology (4 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 500)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Science and Technology (2 folders)
    - Science and Technology--Subcommittee on Energy Research and Development and Demonstration (2 folders)
    - Science and Technology--Energy Research and Development Administration [ERDA] (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 501)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Science and Technology--Subcommittee on Space Science and Applications (2 folders)
    - Small Business Committee
    - Committee on Standards of Official Conduct
    - Veterans Affairs Committee
    - Ways and Means (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 502)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means (3 folders)
    - Ways and Means--Revenue Sharing
    - Ways and Means--Social Security
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 503)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means--Tax Reform (3 folders)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Accomack County
    - Agriculture Department (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 504)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Agriculture Department (2 folders)
    - Air Force
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission [ARBC] (2 folders)
    - AMTRAK
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 505)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Anheuser-Busch
    - Army
    - Assateague
    - Back Bay
    - Cambodia--Mayaguez
    - Central Intelligence Agency [CIA]
    - Census Bureau
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation
    - Chincoteague National Wildlife Refuge
    - Civil Aeronautics Board [CAB]
    - Civil Service Commission
    - Coast Guard
    - Colonial National Historical Park--Yorktown
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 506)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Commerce Department
    - Commerce--Economic Development Administration
    - Community Services Administration
    - Office of Consumer Affairs
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission
    - Corps of Engineers--General (2 folders)
    - Corps of Engineers--Kingsmill on the James
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 507)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Council on Environmental Quality
    - Customs Service
    - Defense Department--General
    - Defense Department--Army National Guard
    - Defense Department--Camp Peary
    - Defense Department--Cape Charles NAVCOMFAC
    - Defense Department--Cheatham Annex
    - Defense Department--Dahlgren
    - Defense Department--Football Tickets--DOD Service Academies
    - Fort Eustis--General
    - Fort Eustis--Transportation Corps Museum Foundation
    - Fort Story
    - Hampton Metro Oil v. Defense Supply Agency
    - Langley Air Force Base (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 508)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Defense Department--Langley Air Force Base (2 folders)
    - Defense Department--Langley AFB Hospital
    - Defense Department--Military Traffic Management Command [MTMC)
    - Defense Department--Radford Ammunition Center
    - Defense Department--Yorktown Naval Weapons Station
    - War and Navy--General, 1958-1961, n.d. (2 folders)
    - War and Navy--A-B (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 509)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - War and Navy--C-Z (I, Q, U, V, X, omitted) (11 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 510)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School
    - Economic Development Administration
    - Environmental Protection Agency [EPA]
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Air Pollution
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Non-refillable Bottles
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Water Pollution
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Severn River Pollution
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission [EEO]
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 511)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Energy Research and Development Administration [ERDA]
    - Exmore
    - Federal Aviation Administration [FAA]
    - Federal Communications Commission [FCC]
    - Federal Energy Administration [FEA]--General (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 512)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Federal Energy Administration--General (2 folders)
    - Federal Energy Administration--Cases
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board
    - Federal Maritime Commission
    - Federal Power Commission [FPC]
    - Federal Trade Commission [FTC]
    - Freshman Congressional Reception by Library Associations
    - General Accounting Office [GAO]
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 513)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - General Services Administration [GSA]
    - Government Printing Office [GPO]
    - Hampton, City of
    - Health, Education and Welfare [HEW]--General (3 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 514)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Health, Education and Welfare--General (1 folder)
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Center of Excellence, Inc.
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Food and Drug Administration
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Health Systems Agency [HSA]
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Office of Education
    - Health, Education and Welfare--National Institutes of Health
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Public Health Service
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 515)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Social Security Administration
    - Highways (2 folders)
    - House of Representatives
    - Housing and Urban Development [HUD] (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 516)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Housing and Urban Development (1 folder)
    - Conference on Hunger
    - Immigration
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service--Richmond
    - Department of the Interior--General (2 folders)
    - Department of the Interior--National Park Service
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 517)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Internal Revenue Service [IRS]
    - Interstate Commerce Commission [ICC]
    - James City County
    - Jewish Federation
    - Justice Department
    - J--General
    - King George County
    - Labor Department (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 518)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Labor Department (1 folder)
    - Library of Congress
    - Lockwood Brothers, Ind.--Pier X, Newport News
    - L--General
    - Maritime Administration [MARAD]
    - Maritime Administration--USS United States--Bicentennial
    - Middlesex County
    - M--General
    - National Advisory Committee on Oceans and Atmosphere
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 519)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration [NASA]
    - NASA--Langley AFB (2 folders)
    - NASA--Space Radiation Effects Laboratory
    - NASA--Wallops Island
    - National Endowment for the Arts--War Memorial Museum
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration [NOAA]
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 520)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - National Science Foundation
    - Department of the Navy--General
    - Department of the Navy--Carpooling--Newport News Ship Building and Dry Dock Co.
    - New Kent County
    - Newport News, City of
    - Northampton County
    - Office of Economic Opportunity [OEO]
    - Office of Management and Budget
    - Page--U.S. Capitol
    - Page School, 1975
    - Patrick Henry Airport
    - Patronage
    - Pocahontas
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 521)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Post Office Files--A-F (B omitted) (5 folders)
    - Post Office Files--General
    - Post Office Files--G-W (K, P, R, T-V, X-Z omitted) (11 folders)
    - Post Office Files--General Postmaster and Post Office Information
    - Post Office Files--Postmasters--A
    - Post Office Files--Postmasters--Cape Charles
    - Post Office Files--Postmasters--C-T (D-F, H-J, O, Q-S, U-Z omitted) (4 folders)
    - Post Office Files--Post Offices--A-E (C omitted) (4 folders)
    - Post Office Files--Post Offices--Fort Monroe
    - Post Office Files--Post Offices--Gloucester and Mathews Star Route
    - Post Office Files--Post Offices--H-P (H, I, K-N omitted) (4 folders)
    - Post Office Files--Post Offices--Rural Routes
    - Post Office Files--Post Offices--Star Routes
    - Post Office Files--Post Offices--S-Z (T-Z omitted) (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 522)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - U.S. Postal Service--General (3 folders)
    - U.S. Postal Service--Commemorative Stamps
    - Lewis B. Fuller Vocational Center
    - P--General
    - Securities and Exchange Commission [SEC]
    - Small Business Administration [SBA]
    - Department of State--General (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 523)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Department of State--General (1 folder)
    - Department of State--Middle East Advisors--Sinai Peace Keeping
    - Summer Intern, 1976
    - Tangier Island
    - U.S. Trade Commission
    - Transportation Department
    - Department of the Treasury
    - Veterans Administration [VA]
    - VA Center Hampton
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 524)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Commonwealth of Virginia (4 folders)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company [VEPCO]
    - VEPCO Economic Studies--Middle Peninsula Planning District
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 525)
  - General Files [and Federal Installations].
    - Virginia General Assembly
    - Virginia State Corporation Commission--Medical Malpractice Insurance
    - Virginia Port Authority
    - Virginia Seafood Council
    - Virginia Soil and Water Conservation
    - Ward v. U.S. Congress--Civil Action #76-H-1259
    - George Washington Birthplace--National Monument
    - Williamsburg, City of
    - Colonial Williamsburg
    - W--General
    - York County
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, January-April 1975 (4 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 526)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, May-December 1975 (4 folders)
    - Invitations Declined, January 1975
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 527)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, February-June 1975 (6 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 528)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, July-November 1975 (6 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 529)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, December 1975
    - Invitations Accepted, January-May 1976 (5 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 530)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, June-November 1976 (6 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 531)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, December 1976
    - Invitations Declined, January-May 1976 (6 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 532)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, June-November 1976 (7 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 533)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, December 1976
    - Weekly Schedules, 1976
    - Week-at-a-Glance, 1976
    - Guest Registers, September 1971-December 1976 (2 folders)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Assateague National Seashore (P.L. 94-578) (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 534)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Assateague National Seashore (5 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 535)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - Electric Vehicles--Demonstration and Feasibility (P.L. 94-413)
    - Housing--Emergency Assistance to Promote (P.L. 94-50)
    - Thomas Jefferson Day, 13 April 1976 (P.L. 94-263)
    - Kennedy Assasination--Committee to Investigate
    - Robert E. Lee--Restore Citizenship (P.L. 94- )
    - Metric Conversion (P.L. 94-168)
    - Missing in Action--Select Committee (P.L. 94- )
    - NASA Authorization (P.L. 94-307)
    - National Family Week (P.L. 94-270)
    - National Hunting and Fishing Day (P.L. 94-96)
    - Postal Service--Closings and Service (P.L. 94- )
    - Public Health Service Act--Medical Personnel Shortages (P.L. 94-484)
    - Railroad Reorganization Act--to Amend (P.L. 94-555)
    - SS United States--Floating Hotel (P.L. 94-536) (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 536)
  - Legislation Enacted.
    - SS United States (1 folder)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Alaska Refuges Act (H.R. 1520)
    - American Business Day--Landing at Jamestown (H.J. Res. 118)
    - Advanced Automobile Propulsion Systems (H.R. 13655)
    - Back Bay Wildlife Refuge--Access for Property Owners (H.R. 8644)
    - Broadcasting Service (H. Res. 1170)
    - Broadcast License Renewal (H.R. 243)
    - Cable Television Systems--Low Cost Loans (H.R. 5310)
    - Carrier, Stephen Carpenter--Dual Citizenship (H.R. 12914)
    - China--Ally--Republic of China (H. Con. Res. 381)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 537)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Contiguous Fishery Zone/Straight Baselines (H.R. 1804)
    - Corps of Engineers Jurisdiction (H.R. 8055)
    - Consumer Communications Reform Act of 1976 (H.R. 14158)
    - Deep Creek-Craney Island Disposal Area (H.R. 14595) (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 538)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Deep Creek-Craney Island Disposal Area (1 folder)
    - Depository Libraries--Law Schools (H.R. 1269; H.R. 15101)
    - ERDA--Assistant Administrator for Solar and Geothermal Energy (H.R. 13409)
    - Federal Courts Jurisdiction--School Attendance (H.R. 14054)
    - Federal Trade Commission--Preempting State-Local Laws (H. Con. Res. 508)
    - FBI Director--Appoint for 15-years/Single Term (H.R. 357)
    - General Schedule Conversion--Employees at Langley AFB (H.R. 248)
    - Guns--Mandatory Sentence for Use in Crime (H.R. 13016)
    - Habeas Corpus--Appeals from State Courts (H.R. 245)
    - Haller, Roswitha--Relief (H.R. 15233)
    - Health Benefits Coverage--Civil Service Employees (H.R. 249)
    - Jefferson--Notable Accomplishments (H.J. Res. 777)
    - Judges--Reconfirmation--8-year Terms (H.J. Res. 44)
    - Labor--Ages 14 to 16 Exempt from Standards--Seafood (H.R. 2186)
    - James Madison--225th Birthday (H.J. Res. 802)
    - Manassas National Battlefield Park (H.R. 9222)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 539)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Maritime Authorization (H.R. 11481)
    - Medical Insurance (H.R. 7129)
    - Medicredit--Health Care Insurance Act (H.R. 2226) (2 folders)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - National Beta Sigma Phi Week (H.J. Res. 917)
    - Optometric and Medical Vision Care (H.J. Res. 9894)
    - Panama Canal--Accounting Standards (H.R. 14311)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 540)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Panama Canal--Retain U.S. Sovereignty and Jurisdiction (H. Res. 127)
    - Patent Law Revision (H.R. 12873)
    - Popular Election of President and Vice-President (H.J. Res. 43)
    - Postal Employees Representative (H.R. 9015)
    - Recomputation of Retired Military Pay (H.R. 1167)
    - Recomputation of Retired Military Pay--Prior to 93rd Congress (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 541)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Recomputation of Retired Military Pay--Prior to 93rd Congress (1 folder)
    - Separation Pay--Regular Enlisted Personnel (H.R. 2185) (2 folders)
    - Select Committee on Narcotics Abuse and Control (H. Res. 1353)
    - Siebel, CDR J.A.--Relief (H.R. 14017)
    - Social Security--Liberalize Disability Benefits Requirements (H.R. 253)
    - Social Security--Disabled and Age 72 (H.R. 252)
    - Social Security--Death Benefits (H.R. 362; H.R. 5868)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 542)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Solar Heating Installation--Direct Low Interest Loans (H.R. 4619)
    - Statute of Limitations--Civil Rights Actions (H.R. 12874)
    - Tax Credit for Tuition (H.R. 361) (2 folders)
    - Investment Tax Credit (H.R. 10551)
    - Tax on Estates and Farm Property (H.R. 6103; H.R. 14115)
    - Tax on Telephone Service (H.R. 251)
    - Tax Benefits--Unmarried and Employed Couples (H.R. 2224)
    - Bicentennial Transportation System (H.R. 3714) (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 543)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Transportation and Travel for Retired Military (H.R. 10991)
    - Truth in Government--Accounting Act of 1975 (H.R. 11080)
    - Unemployment Compensation--Extent (H.R. 13072)
    - United Nations--Limit Contribution by U.S. (H.R. 356)
    - United Nations--Review Relationship with U.S. (H. Res. 889)
    - Veterans Non-service Disability Pension (H.R. 250)
    - Virginia Statute for Religious Freedom (H.R. 15209)
    - de la Vega, Alberto--Relief (H.R. 10724)
    - Washington's Birthplace National Monument (H.R. 9986)
    - Water Bank Act (H.R. 2296)
    - Zionism--Equated with Racism by U.N. (H. Res. 814)
    - Busing Amendment (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 544)
  - Legislation Not Enacted.
    - Busing Amendment (1 folder)
    - Possible Legislation, 94th Congress
    - General Information File
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, various sessions.
  - Master Files.
    - 1st Session, A-D (6 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 545)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st Session, E-M (11 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 546)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st Session, N-Z (X omitted) (13 folders)
    - 2nd Session, A
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 547)
  - Master Files.
    - 2nd Session, B-Mc (12 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 548)
  - Master Files.
    - 2nd Session, M-Z (X omitted) (14 folders)
    - Master File Galley
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Clippings--Downing, January-February 1975 (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 549)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Clippings--Downing, March-December 1975 (10 folders)
    - Clippings--General, January-December 1975 (12 folders)
    - Clippings--Downing, January-April 1976 (4 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 550)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Clippings--Downing, May-December 1975 (8 folders)
    - Clippings--General, January-December 1976 (12 folders)
    - Clippings--Thomas N. Downing Retirement, 1976
    - Political Newspaper Clippings, 94th Congress (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 551)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Political Newspaper Clippings, 94th Congress (1 folder)